[{"answer": "What did I tell you? What did I tell you? Buy the road map and leave", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "He didn't recognize shit", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Why, just look at all this. You got your kitchen", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "-- you got your sink", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "-- you got your microwave", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "-- you got your shower", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "They don't have anything except four walls and a roof, and that's all we need", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "We've received no news one way or the other. We can only hope for the best", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "This can't be confirmed at this time, but we do believe it to be true. We have reason to believe it was the youngest brother my friend, and he was shot in the vicinity of his neck and shoulders by the store's clerk", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong! Once you left, she became a whole different person", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It's not your fault, it's her fault", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yes, my friend, I understand", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "There's nothing wrong with this place", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It's not a flop house. It's basic and simple. That doesn't make it a flop house", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He's my son", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Neither does he. He looks Vietnamese", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Sorry, I need everybody", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " That's not fuckin' that...  this is fuckin' this.  Go sit over there", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Where are you taking us", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What's in that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You're a preacher", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Was? As in not anymore", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No, I didn't", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You must have a bible in here, don't cha", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Get it and bring it up here, will ya, please", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Swear to God, on the Bible, you won't try to escape and you'll get us across the border", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You best better get it done, Pops", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Do what", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " What did I say", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What are you gonna do", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No, dad, you gotta tell 'em that they're back there", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "They're gonna kill us. They get us across the border, they're gonna take us out in the desert and shoot us", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Dad, I watch those reality shows. They never let anybody go. Any cop will tell you, in a situation like this, you get a chance, you go for it. This is our chance", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm in the bathroom", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It's open", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'm lookin' scared", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You know what you look like", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "That's what you look like", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No, my friend, what do I look like", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " Take your hand off me", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "No, I'm going to count to three", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Whatsamatter with you? Are you crazy", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I don't know, one place's as good as another", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "It's hardly been used at all. I got it from a drug dealer who only drove it 5 times in as many years. Swear to God. That's like new", "docId": "From-Dusk-Till-Dawn.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Yeah, follow us", "qsentId": 48}]